加州  薩克拉門托  克里斯托弗酒店
頭兒
Hi, boss.
司機遭受嚴重割傷
Driver sustained heavy lacerations
以及頭部外傷  但據他們說
and head trauma, but believe it or not,
他會活下去的
they're saying he'll live.
幸運的人
Lucky.
死者名叫莎倫·沃里克  二十三歲
Victim's Sharon Warwick, 23.
她是從914號房的陽臺摔下來的
She went off of a balcony, Room 914.
瑞斯比現在正跟鑒證小組在上面
Rigsby's up there right now with the forensics team.
從死者臉頰上的淤青和被撕開的背心來看
Now off the bruise on the cheek and the ripped vest,
這是起謀殺案
we're thinking it's murder.
她是餐廳服務員
Catering staff?
事實上  她是劇組成員
Actually, she was a cast member.
音樂劇《火炬》
Show's called "Torch".
講述了上世紀五十年代紐約一家夜總會中
It's a story about intersecting lives and loves
生命與愛情相互交織的故事
in a New York night club in the 1950s.
今晚的晚宴是為演出募款
The event tonight was a fund-raiser for the show.
多名目擊者稱死者死亡時間是晚上八點零一分
Multiple witnesses say the time of death is 8:01 p.m.,
就在表演正要開始的時候
right when the performance was set to begin.
上面發生了什么事
Well, what was she doing up there?
目前還不清楚
We don't know yet.
是制片人沃倫·道奇認出她的
She was I.D.'d by Warren Dodge, the producer.
他跟導演在里面
He's in there with the director.
好的
All right.
可憐的莎倫
Poor Sharon.
悲劇  太悲劇了
Tragedy. Absolute tragedy.
但我們要重整旗鼓
But you know what? We're gonna regroup,
我們會度過這一切的  布蘭
and we'll move forward from this, Bran,
我們會更好更強的  你看著吧
better and stronger. You'll see.
沃倫  我們的女主角正坐在出租車里爛醉如泥
Warren, our star is in a cab blotto,
女二號死了
our second lead is dead.
我們怎么可能更好更強
How do you propose we do better and stronger?
-布蘭  聽著  -道奇先生
- Bran, listen-- - Uh, Mr. Dodge?
-什么事  -我是里斯本探員
- Yes? - I'm Agent Lisbon.
我需要問你幾個問題
I need to ask you some questions.
好的  當然  你能稍微給我點時間嗎
Of course. Of course. Can you give me just one minute?
布蘭  我們要把《火炬》帶到百老匯去
Bran, we are going to get "Torch" to Broadway.
相信我  好嗎
We are, all right?
我來處理投資方的事
I'll take care of the investors.
漢諾威很可靠  這樣一半的錢就有了
Hanover is solid, that's 50% of our money.
這樣就只需要擔心其他那些投資商了  對吧
It's only the other investors we have to worry about, all right?
你的任務
Your job is to keep calm
就是去安撫演員和工作人員  好嗎
and reassure the cast and crew, all right?
道奇先生
Mr. Dodge.
-是的  -你是
- Yes? - And you are?
布蘭·麥克塔維什  我是導演
Uh, Bran McTavish, the director.
你們兩位有親眼看到莎倫·沃里克墜樓嗎
Did either of you actually see Sharon Warwick fall?
我在里面  演出要開始了
I was inside. The show was starting.
我到的時候
And I arrived
慘劇已經發生了
right after it happened.
你們知道
Do you have any idea
她為何去914房嗎
what she was doing up in room 914?
那塊區域是我們這次演出用的化妝室
Well, we were using that area as a dressing room for this event.
她本應在下面的宴會大廳的
She was supposed to be down in the ballroom.
她第三個出場
She was third cue.
-第三個出場  -對
- Third cue? - Yeah.
我們讓演員零零散散地
We had, uh, actors scattered about
裝扮成酒店客人  工作人員和餐廳服務員
dressed as hotel guests, workers, caterers.
開場是布蘭的創意
It was Bran's idea to start the show.
對  一個客人突然出來唱歌
Yeah, a guest breaks out into song,
然后是侍者  再是女服務員
then the bellboy, then the waitress.
就是莎倫
That was Sharon.
她該呆在宴會大廳的
She was supposed to be in the ballroom.
你們幫了大忙
You've both been really helpful.
如果可以的話  請你們在我們調查時
If you wouldn't mind going up to the room
到上面的房間來
while we start the investigation,
謝謝
I'd be grateful.
我們定當盡力
Anything we can do.
里斯本
Hey, Lisbon.
你到底去哪里了
Where the hell are you?
別跟我說你在醫院
Don't tell me you're at the hospital.
我沒在醫院
I'm not at the hospital.
有案子了
We caught a case.
你得到案發現場來
You're needed at the crime scene.
我馬上到
I'll be there soon.
你在醫院  對吧
You're at the hospital, aren't you?
是你讓我不要告訴你
You told me to tell you
我在醫院的
I'm not at the hospital.
你到底想怎樣  想清楚
What do you want? Make up your mind.
離開那兒
Get out of there.
如果杰森·列儂醒了
If Jason Lennon wakes up,
如果他開口了
and if he talks,
如果他知道血腥約翰的身份
and if he knows Red John's identity,
柯克蘭探員和國土安全局
Agent Kirkland and Homeland Security
一定能妥善處理的
are perfectly capable of handling it.
我不同意
I disagree.
你這是在玩火
You're playing with fire.
還有更壞的呢
There are worse things to play with.
我得掛了
Oh, gotta go.
柯克蘭探員
Ah, Agent Kirkland.
你怎么進來的
How did you get in?
這片區域謝絕探訪者
This wing is closed to visitors.
我的阿姨戴芬住在十號病房
My Aunt Daphne's in room 10.
腎衰竭  可憐人  酗酒害的
Kidney failure. Poor dear. Drinks like a fish.
你一定為此心碎了吧
You must be broken up about it.
看看你  一團糟
Look at you. You're a mess.
我們都清楚你為何來這兒
We both know why you're here.
不過我很好奇為什么你急著要和列儂談話
Although I find your need to talk to Lennon now interesting.
勞拉蕾·馬丁斯槍擊他的時候你可袖手旁觀了
You did stand by while Lorelei Martins shot him.
他怎么樣了
How's he doing?
他會活著跟我們談話的
He'll live to talk to us.
如果他說了什么有趣的事  我會告訴你的
And I'll let you know if he has anything interesting to say.
跟你談話總是很愉快  派翠克
You're always good to talk to you, Patrick.
但是我覺得你應該離開了
But I think you should go now,
在我們打擾到病人休息之前
before we start disturbing the patients.
這邊走  先生
This way, sir.
我自己會走  這是我的手臂
Yeah. I'm going. That's my arm.
你自己有好好的兩條手臂呢  放開我謝謝
You have two of your own. Thank you.
你到底怎么進來的
How did you get in here?
誰讓你進來的
Who let you in?
如果我告訴你了  我下次再來的時候
Well, if I told you that, I wouldn't be able to get in
就進不來了  不是嗎
when I come back, would I?
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
人人影視
YYeTs.com
■
翻譯：灰灰菇涼 王利崢是小交交 蘇慕晴天 芒果妖怪 爬爬 非燕 那時花開
超感警探
第五季
第十八集
■
時間軸：煙幕遲遲  luvkobe   校對/精校：灰灰是菇涼  王小麥
第五季
第十八集
■
特效&后期：灰灰是菇涼   校對&總監：灰灰是菇涼
有誰能進到
Uh, did anybody have access
莎倫旁邊的套房
to the suite besides Sharon?
這片區域是用作這次晚會的公共更衣室
This served as a sort of communal dressing area for this event,
所以所有人都能進
so, everybody, really.
所有的演員加上我  道奇和西爾維亞
The whole cast plus myself, Dodge, and, uh, Sylvia.
你聯系漢諾威了嗎
Hey, um, have you spoken to Hanover?
我希望他是從我們這兒最先得知此事的
I wanna make sure he hears about this from us first.
西爾維亞  你去擔心其他的投資商
Uh, Sylvia, you worry about the other investors.
讓我來處理漢諾威  好嗎
Let me deal with Hanover, all right?
這位是西爾維亞·克萊爾  我們的公關
Um, this is Sylvia Clare, our publicist.
西爾維亞  這位加調局的里斯本探員
Sylvia, uh, Agent Lisbon is with the CBI.
誰是漢諾威
Who's Hanover?
我們的贊助人  主要投資商
Our patron. Our main investor.
簡  你來了
Oh, Jane, there you are.
這位是...
This is the--
不用介紹了  我在電梯里過了一遍
No need. I just caught up in the elevator.
道奇  麥克塔維什  克萊爾
Uh, Dodge, McTavish, and Clare,
制片人  導演  公關
producer, director, publicist.
莎倫和其他演員或工作人員有什么矛盾嗎
Was Sharon having any trouble with the, uh, cast or crew?
不  不  一點也沒有
No, no. Not at all.
我們《火炬》劇組是個大家庭
We're a very happy family here at "Torch."
當然了  一個好公關
Yes, of course. That's exactly what a good publicist
就應該這么說  對吧
should say, isn't it?
受害人墜樓時你在哪  克萊爾小姐
Uh, where were you when the victim fell, Ms. Clare?
我在宴會大廳
Oh, I was in the ballroom.
道奇先生  你為什么要讓
Mr. Dodge, uh, what made you want
莎倫·沃里克演女二號
to cast Sharon Warwick as the second lead?
根據這上面來看  她沒有多少戲劇經驗
According to this, she doesn't have much theater experience.
她這段介紹挺短的
Her paragraph's very short.
莎倫從紐約來
Well, uh, Sharon came out here from New York,
她試鏡的時候征服了布蘭
and she just knocked Bran out with her audition.
我信任他的判斷力
And, uh, I trust his judgment.
她是個天生的舞者  聲音洪亮
She's a natural dancer, big voice,
學得快  急欲成長
quick learner, and she was hungry.
這就夠了
That's all you need.
她有什么好處
Well, what was in it for her?
我是說  大材小用了
I mean, it's a revival in the sticks.
她在紐約已經是歌星了
She was already a well-known singer in New York.
她想嘗試一些特別的東西
She wanted to be a part of something special.
確實如此  我們在薩克拉門托首映
Exactly. I mean, we're starting out here in Sacramento,
但是《火炬》六個月后就會登上百老匯
but "Torch" will be on Broadway in six months.
九個月后會成為托尼獎競爭者
And a Tony contender in nine.
演員們和當地人有什么接觸嗎
Did the cast have much contact with the locals?
不知道  我認為沒有
Uh, I don't know. I don't-- I don't think so.
我覺得他們沒有時間
Oh, I wouldn't think they'd have the time.
他們肯定馬上開始彩排了
They would have been right into rehearsals straightaway.
-是的  很對  -好吧
- Yeah. That's right. - So, yeah.
那么你跟我想的一樣
So you think like me.
兇手和你的音樂劇有關聯
The killer is connected to your musical.
有什么想法嗎
Any guesses?
沒有  好吧  謝了
No? Okay. Thanks.
不好意思  他是誰
I'm sorry. Who is that?
他是個顧問
He's a consultant.
謝謝你們合作
Thank you for your time.
嫌疑人太多了
The suspect pool is huge.
這會跟噩夢一樣
It's gonna be a nightmare.
怎么一開始就這么消極
Why start on such a pessimistic foot?
你為什么悶悶不樂的
Why are you so glum?
我給你打電話  你卻在圍著列儂轉
I call you up, and you're creeping around Lennon,
試圖插手柯克蘭的工作
getting into Kirkland's business.
我當然悶悶不樂了
Of course I'm glum.
-因為這個啊  -是的  因為這個
- Oh, that. - Yeah. That.
勞拉蕾·馬丁斯這事兒上我們已經顏面盡失了
We look bad enough after the whole Lorelei Martins mess.
列儂是找到血腥約翰的直接線索
Lennon is a direct link to Red John.
我得跟他談談
I need to talk to him.
你要學會守規矩
You need to try and start following the rules for a while.
如果你非要不按規矩辦事
And if you must break the rules,
那就用你自己的時間
break them on your own time.
什么時候不是我自己的時間
When am I not on my own time?
格蕾斯
Grace.
見到你真高興
It's so good to see you.
洛杉磯怎么樣
How was L.A.?
學到不少好東西
I learned a lot of really great stuff,
但我不知道別人是怎么住在那的
but I don't know how anybody lives there.
能回家我很開心
I'm really happy to be home.
歡迎回來工作
Well, welcome back to the grindstone.
謝謝  這音樂怎么回事
Yeah. What's with the music?
我們的死者是名歌手
Our victim's a singer.
她被人從窗口推了下去
She was pushed out of a window.
挺上口的  是吧
It's kind of catchy, huh?
是網絡熱門歌曲
It was an Internet hit.
她來這主演音樂劇  結果被殺了
She comes out here to star in a musical and gets killed.
范佩爾  歡迎回來
Van Pelt! Welcome back.
謝了  頭兒  回來真好
Thanks, boss. It's good to be back.
見到你真好
It's good to see you.
進展怎么樣
How we doing so far?
挺好  發現了沃里克其實是本地人
Good. Found out that Warwick was actually a local.
真的嗎  戲劇公司的人似乎
Really? The people from the theater company
覺得她是紐約來的
seemed to think she was from New York.
我跟一個叫波麗·戴遲的談過了
No, I spoke to a Polly Datch.
她說她是沃里克在薩克拉門托的養母
Said she was Warwick's foster mother here in Sacramento.
她在來加調局的路上
She's on her way to CBI.
案發當晚沃里克的行程是什么
What about Warwick's timeline the night of the murder?
我已經和大概一半的演員談過了
Wll, I've spoken to about half the cast so far.
壞消息是他們為了方便進出  沒有鎖上
Bad news is they were leaving the door to that room unlocked
那房間的門
for ease of access.
所以她死的時候  在場的可能是任何人
So anyone could have been in there when she died?
是的  好消息是我們有很多視頻和照片
Yeah. The good news is we got a whole lot of video
來進行調查工作
and photos to work off.
演員在7點45分左右離開房間
So the cast left the room at around a quarter of 8:00
準備就位
to get into position.
沃里克當時還跟他們在一起
Warwick was with them.
她7點52分離開宴會大廳
She leaves the ballroom at 7:52.
8點01分墜落在轎車上
At 8:01, she hits the limo.
在這期間制片方
Was anyone else from production missing
-有沒有人不見  -目前還不能確定
- during that period? - I can't tell just yet.
我會繼續查
I'll keep digging.
在她墜樓后有人匆忙離開嗎
Did anybody leave in a hurry after she fell?
有一個  迪安德拉·桑德蘭  女主角
Yeah, one. Deandra Sunderland, the star.
演員中有傳言
Now the rumor among the cast
她有酗酒的問題
is that she's got a drinking problem,
他們認為她很可能
so they think she's probably getting sauced
去酒店吧臺喝酒了
in one of the, uh, hotel bars.
有酗酒問題的過氣天后  真不尋常
A fading diva with a drinking problem? That's unusual.
-是啊  看看這個  -這是她離開的時候
- Yeah. Check this out. - This is her leaving.
什么時間
Well, when was that?
案發后半小時
About half-hour after the murder.
賓館的監控錄像呢
Uh, what about the surveillance footage from the hotel?
大廳和電梯有錄像
Cameras in the lobby and all the elevators.
馬上就送到
It's being sent over.
那那個投資商呢  漢諾威
What about the investor-- Hanover?
查到他什么了嗎
Do you have anything on him?
演員說了他很多事情
Yeah, the cast had a lot to say about him, too.
他富得能買下特拉華州
Apparently he can buy Delaware.
在公關送來的錄像中我們可以看到他到場
We also found his arrival in the party footage the publicist sent over.
我在網上查到了他
I looked him up on the Internet.
他是外匯交易員  喜歡藝術
He's a currency trader, and he likes the arts.
頭兒  波麗·戴遲  死者的養母
Hey, boss, Polly Datch, victim's foster mom--
-想跟你談談  -好的
- wants to talk to you. - All right.
戴遲夫人  我是里斯本探員
Uh, Mrs. Datch? I'm Agent Lisbon.
你是莎倫·沃里克的養母嗎
Uh, you were Sharon Warwick's foster parent?
-是的  警官  -多久了
- Yes, ma'am. - Uh, for how long?
莎倫來我家時十二歲
Sharon came to live with me when she was 12.
她不知道她的親生父母
Never knew her biological parents.
我和我大多數的孩子都很親密
I stay close with most of my kids,
但是 莎倫很特別
but Sharon was special.
這是你們要找的人
That's the man you need to find--
貝利·拉辛
Billy Racine.
他是什么人
Who is he?
他是個小混混
No-good thug, that's who.
他是她的前男友嗎
Is he an ex-boyfriend?
那是她做的一個不明智的選擇
He was her one bad choice.
你們回來后
Had she been in contact with Racine
她還有和拉辛聯系嗎
since you came back to town?
肯定有
I'm sure of it.
而且我覺得一周前他打了她
And I think he assaulted her a week ago.
你覺得
You think?
我不能說我知道  因為她不肯提這件事
I don't really know because she wouldn't talk about it.
她氣壞了  說自己是被搶劫了
She bursted off, called it a botched mugging.
但我可以肯定就是他
But I'm certain it was him.
不然她為什么不報案
Why else wouldn't she report it?
他以前有對她動粗過嗎
Had he been violent with her in the past?
莎倫說沒有  但是...
Sharon said no, but...
我知道貝利·拉辛有暴力傾向
I know Billy Racine is a violent man.
當然
Sure.
當然  漢諾威先生  非常感謝
Of course, Mr. Hanover. Thank you for your time.
終于找到漢諾威了
Finally found Hanover?
是啊  他也沒看到事發那一幕
Yeah. He didn't see the crash either,
但他說他回來以后
but he said he'd be happy to talk to us
很樂意和我們談談
when he gets back in town.
回來以后
Back in town?
他飛去參加一個藝術展開幕式了
He had to fly to an art opening.
有一件藝術品他志在必得
A piece he just had to have.
有錢人啊
Rich people.
你查到了什么
What'd you get?
里斯本從她的養母那里得來的
Lisbon got this from the foster mom.
貝利·拉辛  她的前男友
Name's Billy Racine. Ex-boyfriend.
她養母覺得是他做的
Foster mother thinks he could have done it.
這家伙劣跡斑斑啊
Guy's had a life.
多次涉嫌傷害  敲詐
Multiple assaults, extortion.
這名字聽著耳熟
That name sounds familiar.
拉辛  威廉
"Racine. William."
他在演出募款晚宴的入場券
He's on the list of people who purchased tickets
購買者名單上
to the show's fund-raiser.
他去那里做什么
What was he doing there?
我看看能不能找到他
I'll see if I can track him down.
多謝
Thanks.
你兩天前去《火炬》的募款晚宴
What were you doing at the fund-raiser for "Torch"
做什么
two nights ago?
支持藝術啊
Supporting the arts.
你那晚有和莎倫·沃里克聯系嗎
Did you have any contact with Sharon Warwick that evening?
要是有  有什么關系嗎
If I did, what's it matter?
在她去紐約前你們兩個有過
You two had quite the tempestuous relationship
一段相當糟糕的情侶關系
before she moved to New York.
激烈爭吵  你還一拳把墻打穿了
Shouting matches. You even put your fist through a wall.
一個月前她回來的時候
Did you pick up where you left off
你是不是又故態復作了
when she came back a month ago?
別想把這盆臟水潑到我身上
Don't even try to pin this on me.
我知道發生了什么  我沒殺她
I know what's happened, and I didn't kill her.
我為什么要相信你呢
Why should I believe you?
因為我是絕對不會傷害那個姑娘的
Because I would never put my hands on that girl.
我愛她
I loved her.
我覺得也許你愛她太多了
I think you loved her maybe too much.
她拒絕了你
She rejected you,
你不能容忍她的拒絕
you didn't take "No" for an answer,
你跟蹤她到募款晚宴
you stalked her to the fund-raiser.
她再次拒絕了你
And when she rejected you again,
你就氣不過出手殺了她
your hands got the better of you.
我是去保護她的
I went there to protect her.
保護她什么
Protect her from what?
她上周被搶劫了
She got mugged last week.
她反抗了
Said she fought 'em off
而且把其中一個抓傷了
and scratched one of them up pretty good,
但我看得出來她很害怕
but I could see she was shook.
這和募款晚宴有什么關系
What does that have to do with the fund-raiser?
莎倫覺得搶劫是劇組里的某個人設計的
Sharon thought someone from the show set it up.
所以我一聽說她要去那個宴會
So when I heard they were doing that party...
你就去找襲擊她的人
You went to find her attackers?
我本來是要教訓一些人的
I was gonna tune some people up.
可莎倫說"別這樣"  她能處理好
But Sharon said "Be easy." Said she'd handle it.
她有提過她懷疑誰嗎
Did she say who she suspected?
她不肯說
She wouldn't say.
她害怕我會對那些人做出什么不好的事
She was scared I was gonna do something bad to 'em.
她是對的
And she was right.
你是說你們之間一切安好嗎
So you're telling me everything was good between you two?
你和她養母談過了  對吧
You've been talking to that old foster lady, huh?
她從來就不喜歡我
She never liked me.
你不能相信她的一面之辭
You can't believe what she says.
薩克拉門托 表演藝術中心
♪ Ooh-wah, ooh-wah ♪
♪ Why do fools fall in love ♪
停一下  停一下
Okay. One second. One second.
這里是你上場的提示  迪安德拉
Uh, that's your cue, Deandra.
再說一次  為什么我要幫你試鏡替補演員
Tell me again--why am I helping you audition replacements?
因為我們重新安排了給投資商看的演出時間
Uh, well, because our investor performance was rescheduled,
我們必須做好準備
and, uh, we have to be ready.
要是我們能再試一次
So if we could try it one more time,
就再好不過了
that would be wonderful.
我覺得你不是很需要我  布蘭
I-I don't think you really need me for this, Bran, okay?
我先回更衣室了
I'll be in my dressing room.
沒問題
No problem!
好的
Okay, um...
曼迪  布麗奇特  霍華德
Mandy, Bridget, Howard,
從剛才那里開始
uh, from where we left off.
1  2  3
One, two, three.
♪ Love is a losing game ♪
♪ Love can be a shame ♪
♪ I know of a fool you see ♪
♪ For that fool is me ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
抱歉  抱歉  停
Sorry. Sorry. Wait.
彩排是不對外開放的
This is a closed rehearsal.
我們在調查一起謀殺案
Yeah. We're investigating a murder.
那你們在這可找不到什么線索
Well, you won't find any clues here.
實際上  我們可以在觀看排練中
Actually, we could learn a lot
獲得很多信息
from watching a rehearsal.
真的嗎
Oh, really?
是的  一個人唱歌的方式
Yes. The way a person sings
能反映出很多自身的內在
says a great deal about them.
比如說  布麗奇特  你的嗓音很甜美
For instance, Bridget, you have a very sweet tone.
謝謝
Thank you.
帶著粉飾過的憤怒和嫉妒
Yes, with nice shades of pent-up anger and envy.
你應該是討厭莎倫的
You hated Sharon on principle,
你可能就是來取代她的
yet you may come to replace her.
所以很明顯  你有殺她的動機
So obviously, you had very good motive to want to kill her.
但我覺得你沒有把她推下陽臺的
But I don't think you have the stomach or the strength
勇氣和力量
to push someone off a balcony.
你  曼迪  從一方面來說
You, Mandy, on the other hand,
你絕對有完成謀殺的能力
are perfectly capable of murder.
你手段很高
You have a very strong instrument.
你可以演莎倫的部分
You could play Sharon's part.
但你有沒有到非殺她不可的地步呢
But are you hungry enough to kill?
你有那么盛怒嗎
Do you have that kind of passion?
我不知道
I don't know.
別看我了  謝謝
Oh, don't even look at me. Thank you.
得了吧  你不行
Oh, please. Pitchy.
太不行了
Very... pitchy
說完了嗎
You done?
完了  就剩你了  麥克塔維什先生
Yes. Well, that leaves you, Mr. McTavish.
虛榮  控制狂  神經質  自大
Vain. Controlling. Neurotic. Egotistical.
至少和...
Sleeping with, uh,
手下的兩名演員上過床
at least two of your actors.
你是兇手嗎
Are you a killer?
我還不知道你的名字呢
You know, I never did catch your name.
該死
Mm. Damn.
我還以為兇手是你來著
I was sure it was you.
算了  我叫簡
Never mind. Name's Jane.
很高興見到你們  祝你們演出成功
Nice to meet you all. Break a leg.
我覺得你們的歌聲...非常動聽
Well, I thought you sounded... great.
演員的情緒都被他影響了
He's upsetting the performers.
-我知道  我知道  -他會搞砸演出的
I know. I know. He's gonna throw their performances off.
-布蘭  我會處理的  -好吧
- Bran, I'll take care of it. - All right.
可以吧
All right?
簡先生
Mr. Jane.
拜托了  你在場影響了他們的情緒
Please. Your presence isn't good for morale.
大家的狀態似乎還不錯嘛
Everyone seems to be handling it okay.
問題也問完了  你還要待在這里嗎
You've asked your questions. Is it necessary that you remain?
我們不會影響你們的
We'll stay out of your way.
你們都不會發現我們的存在
You'll hardly know we're here.
打擾一下  我和所有
Pardon me. Okay, so I've gotten confirmations
投資方確認過了
from all of our bigger investors.
他們都會出席改期的預演
They will all be at the rescheduled preview.
太好了  漢諾威呢
Excellent. And, uh, Hanover?
還需要再確認一下
Still need to double confirm.
很好  很好
Good. Good.
真是忙碌啊
Busy, busy.
確實
Indeed.
抱歉  我得接個電話
If you'll excuse me, I have to take this.
沒問題
Sure.
打擾一下
Um... Excuse me.
抱歉打擾到你了
Sorry to bother you.
你知道爵士手勢是什么嗎
Uh, I was wondering if you knew what jazz hands were?
當然知道
Sure.
就是舞蹈編排中運用大幅度的手部動作
It's the use of big hand movements in choreography.
為什么這么問
Why do you ask?
我剛剛偶然聽到導演在大吼
Oh, I just overheard the director
說什么爵士手勢
ranting about jazz hands,
所以我就好奇到底是什么讓他這么激動
so I was curious to know what got him so worked up.
他是怎么大吼的
Ranting how?
很顯然  他非常非常討厭爵士手勢
Well apparently, he hate, hate, hates jazz hands.
而且一旦讓他給看到爵士手勢
And if he sees one jazzy little hand,
舞蹈演員就會被踢出表演
that dancer is out of the show.
很高興知道這件事  謝謝
Oh. Good to know. Thanks.
別擔心  你最好把這件事和
No worries. Uh, you might wanna pass that on
你后面那些姑娘說一下
to the girl that comes up after you.
祝你演出成功
Break a leg.
麥姬  到你了
Okay, Maggie, you're up.
我們到底為什么要在這里看試鏡
So what exactly are we looking for with these auditions?
看到就知道了
We'll know when we see it.
你喜歡音樂劇嗎
You like musicals?
沒理由不喜歡啊
Oh, what's not to like?
她們表演得真好
They're so good.
還有多少人
How many more are there?
我也不清楚
I'm not sure.
有個搗蛋鬼應該馬上就要露面了
A troublemaker should reveal herself very shortly.
不  不  不不不不不不不
No! No! No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
你在干什么  布麗奇特
What are you doing, Bridget?
怎么突然就變成了愛達荷的夜店風了
Suddenly we were in a cabaret bar in Idaho.
我以為你希望有大幅度的手部動作
I thought you wanted bigger hand movement.
誰告訴你的
What gave you that idea?
抱歉  不過  這可能是我造成的
Uh, I'm sorry, but this, uh, might indirectly be my doing.
我跟第一個舞者說
I told the first dancer that the director
導演會開除有大幅度手部動作的人
would fire anyone that added big hand movements.
什么
What?
請她  還有所有試鏡的姑娘
And she, along with everyone else who auditioned,
都要告訴自己后面出場的人
made sure that the dancer that came after them
不要做爵士手勢
didn't use the jazz hands
這樣就不會被開除了
so that they didn't lose their job...
除了布麗奇特
until Bridget.
曼迪在我前面
Mandy came before me.
你不是說真的吧
You can't be serious.
只有詭計多端的狡詐的人
Only a scheming and conniving person
才會這么無情地想除去和自己共事的同伴
would so callously try to get a fellow cast mate fired.
真說不準你這種人會做出什么事
There's no telling how far someone like you will go.
他說的是真的嗎  曼迪
Is he telling the truth, Mandy?
這重要嗎
What does it matter?
反正你把手從中間
At least the hands distract away
向兩邊打開的動作也糟透了
from the dreadful syncopation problem you have.
你想我試鏡失敗嗎
You wanted me to fail?
反正也不難
That's not hard.
你個賤人
You bitch.
瑞斯比
Uh, Rigsby?
等等  你剛剛喊我什么來著
Okay. I'm sorry. What did you just call me?
-不好意思  -拿開你的手
- Oh, I'm sorry... - Get your hands off me!
你介意去平息事態嗎
You mind stepping in and handling this?
女士們  女士們  女士們
Ladies, ladies, ladies...
我還有點事
I have an errand to run.
幫幫忙
Help!
好了
Aah! Okay.
我知道你跟我說話就是為了套消息
I know you're only talking to me to get information out of me,
但是你人很好
but it's been nice.
讓我很開心
You make me smile.
還有什么能比得上你的笑容呢
What's worth more than a smile?
說得真對
True enough.
列儂先生的傷勢已經穩定下來了
Mr. Lennon is pretty much stable.
血容量也回升了
His blood volume is up,
明天一早醫生就能讓他從昏迷中
and the doctors could bring him out of the coma
蘇醒過來
as early as tomorrow.
謝謝  很高興了解到這些
Thank you. That's very good to know.
到底是怎么回事
What is all this about?
為什么聯調局的人怪里怪氣又神秘兮兮的
And why are the federal guys so weird and creepy?
是嗎  他們怎么怪里怪氣神秘兮兮的
They are? How are they weird and creepy?
好像他們表里不一
Like they're not what they seem.
好像有一天他們會撕下臉皮
Like one day they might pull their faces off,
露出外星蜥蜴人的臉出來
and there'd be alien lizards underneath, you know?
也不是沒可能  就是可能性很低
I know. Not impossible, but very unlikely.
我知道  他們就是這種德性
I know. They just have that vibe.
是啊
I understand.
他們叫醒列儂先生時  你能通知我嗎
Will you call me when they bring Mr. Lennon out of his coma?
沒問題
Sure.
謝謝  非常感激
Thank you. I appreciate that.
這些抓痕挺引人注目的
Interesting set of scratch marks.
怎么回事
What happened?
貓抓的
Cat.
莎倫·沃里在遭到行兇搶劫的時候反擊過
Sharon Warwick fought back against one of her attackers
其中一名襲擊者
when she was mugged.
你知道嗎
Know anything about that?
你知道謀殺發生后  他們在莎倫的
You know they found D.N.A. samples
指甲里找到了DNA樣本嗎
under Sharon's nails after the murder?
真是神奇啊  一點點DNA
It's amazing how a little D.N.A.
就能把兩個人聯系起來
can tie two people together.
好吧  是我襲擊她的
Okay. The mugging, that was me.
我只是想嚇嚇她
I just wanted to scare her a little bit.
我沒殺她
I didn't kill her.
你的同謀是誰
Who was your accomplice?
一個叫喬伊的人
A guy named Joey.
他是我在薩爾薩舞班上的舞伴
He's my partner in Salsa class.
你為什么想嚇唬她
And why did you want to scare her?
因為她只是個名不見經傳的女孩
Because she was just some girl
聲音不錯  但缺乏經驗
with an okay voice and no resume,
而她竟然跟迪安德拉一起上了頭條
and there she was headlining with Deandra.
那讓你很惱火嗎
And that made you mad?
女二號本應是我  而不是莎倫
Second lead should have been me, not Sharon.
所以當她出席募款晚宴
So when she showed up for the fund-raiser,
準備開始走上成名之路的時候
ready to launch a star-making turn,
你一時沖動  就將她推下了陽臺
you snapped and you pushed her off that balcony.
我說了人不是我殺的
I told you I didn't kill her.
你已經承認策劃了那場襲擊
Well, you've already admitted to organizing an assault.
懷疑你一不做二不休
Why is it so crazy to think
把她殺了也是非常合理的
that you didn't decide to finish the job?
因為我并不想要她的命
Because I didn't want her dead,
我只想讓她離開
I just wanted her to leave.
如果你要找嫌疑犯
If you're looking for suspects,
最好去查查演出的領銜主演
you might wanna check out the star of the show.
迪安德拉·桑德蘭嗎
Deandra Sunderland?
卑鄙女王
The queen of mean.
你為什么認為桑德蘭會殺了沃里克
What makes you think Sunderland could have killed Warwick?
因為導演想讓莎倫取代迪安德拉
Because the director wanted to replace Deandra with Sharon.
所有人都知道
Everybody knew it.
她年紀太大了  不適合扮演天真少女角色了
I mean she's too old to be playing the ingenue, right?
謀殺當晚  你見過桑德蘭嗎
Did you see Sunderland the night of the murder?
沒有
No.
序曲開始的時候  到處都找不到她
She was nowhere to be found when the overture began.
意外發生之后呢
What about after the accident?
她直到第二天早上的排練才出現
Not until rehearsal the next morning.
♪ Every time ♪
♪ we say goodbye ♪
♪ I die♪
♪ a little ♪
♪ Every time ♪
♪ we say goodbye ♪
♪ I wonder why ♪
♪ a little ♪
是的  漢諾威先生  太好了
Yes, Mr. Hanover. Excellent.
好的  不  那聽起來很好
Yeah. Yes. No, that sounds good.
好  聽起來不錯  沒問題
Uh, okay. Sounds good. Sure.
期待盡快見到您  謝謝
We'll see you very soon. Thanks.
抱歉  你們打算把曼迪關多久
Sorry. Um, how long you gonna keep Mandy?
得關一陣子  對待犯法的人就要這樣
A while. That's what we do when people break the law.
探員  我是專業人士
Okay, look, agent, I'm a pro.
我能夠扭轉這場災難
I can spin this tragedy.
它甚至可讓作品更吸引人
It can even add an air of fascination to the production.
但是  如果你們
But if you arrest the cast
在給投資商的演出進行之前逮捕演員的話
right before a performance for the investors,
那會讓我的工作陷入困境
that makes my job rather difficult.
我得讓投資商們保持興趣
You see, I need my investors to stay... invested.
那先給你打個預防針
Well, brace yourself,
因為我要去找迪安德拉·桑德蘭問話了
because now I need to talk to Deandra Sunderland.
這可真是場噩夢
This is a nightmare.
♪ There's no love song ♪
♪ finer ♪
♪ But how strange ♪
♪ the change ♪
♪ from major to minor ♪
桑德蘭女士
Miss Sunderland.
抱歉打斷了你
My apologies for interrupting.
我們得談談
We need to talk.
我正在排練  我希望不被打擾
I'm rehearsing here. I asked not to be disturbed.
這很重要
This is important.
莎倫·沃里克墜下陽臺的時候你在哪里
Where were you when Sharon Warwick fell off the balcony?
我在宴會大廳
I was in the ballroom.
所有的證據都和你的說法相反
All of our evidence points to the contrary.
每一個和演出相關的人
Everybody involved in the production
都覺得你是跑去喝酒了
seems to think you were off drinking.
我認為你有可能和莎倫在一起
I think you might have been with Sharon.
我認為你發現了麥克塔維什打算
I think you found out that McTavish was planning
讓她來取代你  然后你很惱火
on replacing you with her, and you got mad.
他想讓莎倫取代我嗎
He wanted Sharon to replace me?
她在學習你所有表演的錄像
She was studying film of all of your performances
并且在背你的臺詞
and memorizing your lines.
你根本不理解
You don't understand.
你如果告訴她實情  她就會理解了
She would if you told her the truth.
你的歌聲很美
You sing beautifully.
你在那待多久了
How long have you been out there?
很久了
Long enough.
我一直在想  是什么讓莎倫·沃里克
You know, I kept wondering what brought Sharon Warwick
回到薩克拉門托
back to Sacramento.
她為了自己的追求離開薩克拉門托
She left Sacramento because she wanted something,
現在她回來了
and now she's back.
顯然是和《火炬》有關
It's obviously connected to "Torch,"
但她所追尋的東西并不是觀眾的喝彩
but it couldn't be acclaim she was looking for,
因為那她在紐約已經實現了
'cause she got that in New York City.
后來我聽到你唱歌  我才明白
And then I heard you sing, and it came to me.
每個被收養的孩子都在尋找的是什么
What is it that every foster child is looking for?
里斯本  這位是莎倫·沃里克的親生母親
Lisbon, I'd like you to meet Sharon Warwick's mother.
我有莎倫的時候
I was, uh...
還非常年輕
very young when I had Sharon.
她父親是我的導演  他已經結婚了
Her father was my director, and he was married.
把她送走是我人生中最艱難的決定
The hardest thing I ever did in my life was giving her away.
你什么時候知道她是你女兒的
When did she learn she was your daughter?
她在第一天排練之后
She came to my dressing room
來到我的更衣室
after the first day of rehearsals.
你一定很震驚吧
Must have been a shock.
我很高興她的成長
I felt so happy seeing the person that she had become.
她那么有才華
So talented, so...
充滿活力
full of life.
你為什么保密呢
Why did you keep it a secret?
內疚  羞愧
Guilt. Shame.
還有其它的原因
Something else.
你在隱瞞其它原因
You're hiding something else.
你真是個聰明的警察
You're quite a clever policeman, aren't you?
我在六個月前被診斷出
I have multiple sclerosis,
患有多發性硬化癥
diagnosed six months ago.
我很遺憾
Hmm. I'm sorry.
疾病的癥狀
Symptoms of the disease is what
讓人們以為你在酗酒
made people think you were drinking.
我已經戒酒十四年了
Well, I've been sober for 14 years,
至今滴酒未沾
haven't touched a drop.
我聽到別人在我背后的竊竊私語
I heard the whispers behind my back,
覺得是時候離開了
I thought it might be better to quit.
莎倫很生氣
Sharon was so mad,
對我愛護備至
already protective towards me.
她告訴我要堅強
She told me to be strong.
你在第一場演出之前
And you had an attack
疾病發作了  是嗎
right before the first performance, didn't you?
你沒帶藥
You didn't have your medication.
是的
Yes.
莎倫說她會去樓上套房里幫你拿藥
Sharon said she'd go up to the suite and get it for you.
她是個驚人的小姑娘
She was an incredible young woman.
所以我沒法棄演
That's why I can't quit the show.
我不得不繼續
I have to go on with it--
來祭奠我的孩子
to honor my child.
早
Morning.
-早  -早
- Morning. - Morning.
我們查了所有的照片  視頻
We've been through all the photos, videos,
和監控錄像
and security footage.
比對了每個來賓  酒店工作人員
Cross-indexed every guest, hotel worker,
出席者  以及演出相關人員
attendee, and person connected to the play.
所有人的行程都能證實  除了他
All their movements are accounted for, except for him.
伯恩特·漢諾威  那個投資商
Berndt Hanover, the investor?
這是他在兇案發生前
He, uh, here he is before the murder,
在進電梯
getting into the elevator.
他去了莎倫·沃里克遇害的樓層
He goes to the floor Sharon Warwick was killed on
然后下來  之后就不見了
and gets off, and that's the last time we see him.
什么意思  怎么可能
What do you mean? How can that be?
不知道  他再也沒上電梯
I don't know. He never gets back on the elevator,
也沒人見到他離開大樓
and he's never seen leaving the building.
好  可怎么會  為什么  他怎么做到離開大樓
Okay, but how? Why? How does he leave the building
而不被人看到的
without being seen?
如果他等到走廊沒人
If he waited until the hallway was empty,
他可能走下樓到一層
he could've taken the stairs down to the first floor.
就算是這樣  他之后怎么躲過別人的視線
Yeah, but how does he avoid being seen after that?
他又不是什么不起眼的小人物
It--it's not like he's a guy who doesn't stand out.
沒錯
True.
這是案發的房間
This is the room the murder took place.
那里是陽臺  門口通往走廊
That's the balcony. Doorway out here to the corridor.
走樓梯  下去坐電梯
Past the stairs, down to the elevators.
如果我沒記錯  這里是通往消防梯的窗戶
This, if I recall, was a window out to a fire escape.
他可能從消防梯下去嗎
Could he have gone down a fire escape?
他塊頭很大  我覺得他身手沒那么敏捷
He's a big man. I don't think he's that agile.
那怎么回事
Then what?
對  這是個謎題
Hmm. Yes, it's a puzzle.
你怎么看上去那么高興
Why do you look so happy?
你有辦法解開這個謎題
You have a way to solve the puzzle?
那是自然
Naturally.
劇院見
Meet me at the theater.
干得好
This is good work.
及時向我匯報進展
Keep me informed of your progress.
你在門口偷偷摸摸干什么呢  簡先生
Why are you lurking out there, Mr. Jane?
我要你幫忙
I need a favor.
是不是我幫了你的忙
Is this the type of favor where...
你就欠我個人情
You would then owe me a favor?
實際上  你已經欠我個人情了
Actually, you already owe me a favor,
可如果你高興  我可以另借你個人情
but I'll spot you another if that pleases you.
你要什么
What do you need?
要你
I need you.
好  還有十五分鐘開幕  各位
Okay, 15 minutes to curtain, people.
加油  加油
Let's pick it up, pick it up.
迪安德拉  別忘了在第一個前奏時
Um, hey, Deandra, uh, don't forget to wait
等三個小節  好嗎
three bars in the first intro, okay?
親愛的  我在你學會擦鼻子之前
Darling, I've been doing this since before you learned
就已經在這一行了
to wipe your own nose.
管好自己的事吧
Worry about your own business.
別指導  別指導
Never direct. Never direct.
女士們  先生們  請各位有序入場
Ladies and gentlemen, if you will kindly enter the theater
并就座
and take your seats, please.
里斯本  你到劇場了嗎
Hey, Lisbon, you at the theater yet?
簡  你在哪兒
Jane, where are you?
在路上  快到了
Uh, on my way. Almost there.
你去后臺  我們馬上去找你
You head backstage. We'll see you in a minute.
我們  還有誰
We? Who's we? Uh...
很快就見到了  里斯本  再見
I'll see you very soon, Lisbon. Bye.
我心里真沒底
I don't know about this.
相信我  你會覺得很有意思
Oh, trust me. You'll have fun.
"相信我  你會覺得很有意思"
"Trust me. You'll have fun."
還有什么情況會這更可疑
Was there ever a more suspicious phase?
J.J.  你該給生活找點樂子
J.J., you have to live a little.
你每天都在抓小偷
You spend your days chasing paper clip thieves.
什么時候能有機會揪住兇手
When do you ever get the chance to nail a killer?
是沒有
No, it's true.
我很樂意幫忙
I'm happy to help.
我擔心的是我的表現
It's the performance aspect that concerns me.
什么表現
What performance aspect?
你進入房間
You go into a room.
如果有人和你說話
If someone says anything to you,
你就說  "哈哈哈"  或"可能吧"...
you say, "Ha ha ha", or "perhaps"...
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha.
可能吧
Perhaps.
夠了
Good enough.
要帶口音嗎
Would an accent help?
簡單就好
Keep it simple.
你們都知道  這場演出
As you know, this, uh, show
在過去的幾天里
has faced a great deal of hardship and tragedy
遭遇了極大的困難和災難
the past few days.
可我能告訴你們  這只會讓我們變得更強
But I can tell you that it has only made us stronger.
-謝謝  -晚上好  里斯本  找到樂子了嗎
- Thank you. - Evening, Lisbon, you having fun yet?
你來了  剛才去哪里了  你有什么計劃
There you are. Where have you been and what's your plan?
等一下告訴你
I will tell you in one minute.
晚上好  真是個美好的夜晚
Oh, good evening, and what an evening it is.
里斯本  你認識道奇先生嗎
Lisbon, you remember Mr. Dodge?
當然
Of course.
兩位警探  有事嗎
Agents, what are you doing here?
我告訴你  道奇先生
Well, I've gotta tell you, Mr. Dodge,
看了那么多場彩排
after watching all those rehearsals,
我們欲罷不能  可以看表演嗎
we couldn't just stay away, could we?
好  沃倫  你該上臺說話了
Okay, uh, Warren, you're supposed to go say something.
好  我知道  我準備好了
Yes, I know. I'm ready.
最后  有請我們尊敬的制片人
Finally, let me introduce our esteemed producer,
沃倫·道奇  來講話
Warren Dodge, to tell you...
那是誰
Who is that?
天吶  是伯恩特·漢諾威
Oh, my goodness. It's Berndt Hanover.
漢諾威先生
Mr. Hanover. Hi.
真讓人驚喜
What a wonderful surprise.
漢諾威先生  真榮幸
Mr. Hanover, such an honor.
我是西爾維亞·克萊爾  我們通過電話
I'm--I'm Sylvia Clare. We spoke on the phone.
旅途還順利吧
Your trip was a good one, I hope?
是的  很順利  謝謝  克萊爾女士
Yes, it was very good. Thank you, Ms. Clare.
-好  -請問
- Sure. - Excuse me.
怎么回事
What's going on?
沃倫  你怎么不出來跟可愛的觀眾們說說話
Warren? Why don't you come out and talk to the lovely people?
克萊爾女士  我是來給我的投資者們
Ms. Clare, I have come to address
發表講話的
my fellow investors.
不如我去給他們說說話
Why don't I go and speak to them now?
什么
What?
太好了  真是個好主意
Oh, terrific. That is a great idea.
-不是嗎  沃倫  -你是誰
- Isn't it, Warren? - Who are you, huh?
怎么了  等等  你在干什么
W-w-w-whoa. Wait. What are you doing?
他不是伯恩特·漢諾威  他是冒牌貨
He's not Berndt Hanover. He's a fraud!
沃倫  怎么回事
Warren! What is going on?
我不知道他在耍什么把戲
I don't know what game he's playing,
反正他不是漢諾威
but he's not Hanover.
你在說什么  不然他是誰
Well, what are you saying? Then who is he?
他叫J.J.拉羅徹
His name is J.J. LaRoche.
道奇先生說得對  他不是伯恩特·漢諾威
Mr. Dodge is correct. It isn't Berndt Hanover.
好吧  我一頭霧水
Okay, I'm totally confused.
我們偽裝了他  帽子和眼鏡
Ah, we faked it--the hat, the glasses,
手杖  大衣
the cane, the coat.
瞧  伯恩特·漢諾威出現了
Et voila. Berndt Hanover.
可是這是為了什么
But why?
做個測試  你們都以為是他
A test. You all believe it was him,
而且讓你們相信易如反掌
and it was easy to make you believe it.
可好景不長  他把我拆穿了
For about ten seconds, until he said that I wasn't.
然后你們就沒人相信是他了
And then nobody believed it anymore,
而我也不再相信
just like I don't believe anymore
這世界上有伯恩特·漢諾威這個人存在
that Berndt Hanover exists.
什么  太荒唐了
What? Well, that's ridiculous.
-是嗎  -當然有伯恩特·漢諾威這個人了
- Is it? - Of course Berndt Hanover exists.
那就叫他出來吧
Then produce him.
你不是這方面的專家嗎  他在哪兒呢
You're a producer. Where is he?
我總不能把他變出來吧
Well... I just can't magically make him appear.
給他打電話
Call him.
簡先生  我手邊沒他的電話號碼
Mr. Jane, I don't have his phone number on me.
難以置信
Hard to believe.
在我辦公室呢
You know, uh, it's at my office,
我等會兒去那兒打給他
and I will call him there, uh, when I'm--
-我有  我來打  -還好
- I have it. I'll call him. - That's lucky.
-我打了  -很好
- I'm calling him. - Good idea.
-通了  -太好了
- It's ringing. - Excellent.
他可能不會接  他很忙的
He might not answer. He's a--he's a very busy man.
那是
Of course.
打擾一下
Excuse me.
你的衣服在演奏《第五交響曲》呢
Your coat is playing the "Fifth Symphony."
不接嗎  道奇先生
Gonna answer that, Mr. Dodge?
還是該稱你為
Or should we call you mister...
漢諾威先生
Hanover?
你好  抱歉
Hello? Sorry.
道奇先生現在沒空接電話  西爾維亞
Mr. Dodge can't come to the phone right now, Sylvia.
他正忙著被抓起來呢
He's a little busy getting arrested.
漢諾威沒坐電梯下樓
Hanover didn't come down in the elevator,
因為漢諾威這人根本就不存在
because Hanover never even existed.
道奇從一開始就扮上了
Dodge was playing the part from the beginning.
他撕下偽裝
He took off his disguise,
為躲避攝像頭  從逃生梯下樓
eluded the cameras by coming down a fire escape.
里斯本  他歸你了
Lisbon, he's all yours.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
有意思吧
Tell me that wasn't fun.
談不上  不過咱倆扯平了吧
I cannot tell you that, but we are even, yes?
扯平了
Yes.
只要能讓演出打響  我什么都豁得出去
I wanted the show to work. I was willing to do anything.
殺人都不在話下嗎
Even kill?
我
W... I...
她嚇了我一跳
She surprised me.
我當時想換掉扮演漢諾威的那身行頭
When I was changing out of the Hanover costume,
那會兒那個房間里不應該有人
nobody was supposed to be in the room at that time.
一個人都不該有
Nobody.
我跟她說  我為這場演出傾盡了所有
I told her that I put every penny I had into the show
需要有漢諾威這么個人  給投資商信心
and that Hanover was necessary to give our investors a confidence
給他們吃下定心丸
and peace of mind
我告訴她  只要我賺足了錢
and that once I had the money I needed,
就會讓漢諾威消失
I would make Hanover disappear
最終一切都會迎刃而解
and that everything would work out in the end.
但她不肯
But she said no.
她不想參與
She wouldn't be any part of it...
她說要告訴桑德蘭
That she was going to tell Sunderland,
那一切自然就穿幫了
which of course meant that everyone would find out
全都毀了
and... that would have ruined everything.
真的  我沒想到會變成這樣
Yeah. I didn't mean for this to happen.
接下來發生了什么
So what happened next?
我從逃生梯逃走了  沒被人看見
Uh, I left by the fire escape. No one saw me.
然后到了我停在街角的車里
And then I went and got in my car around the corner,
再把車開回來  見到了警察
and I drove up and introduced myself to the police.
這場演出要是一炮而紅  我就能重回巔峰了
This was gonna be the hit show that put me back on top.
本來可以皆大歡喜的
Everyone would have benefited.
要是她沒走進那扇門就好了
If only she hadn't walked through that door.
我跟她在一起的時間很少
I, um, I didn't have nearly enough time with her.
但我非常愛她  很佩服她
But I so loved the person that she was and respected her.
謝謝你們為她主持公道
Thank you for giving her justice.
這對我意義重大
It means a lot.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不好意思  我得接個電話
Embarrassing. Uh, I have to take this.
-失陪  -接吧
- Excuse me. - Of course.
-你好  -派翠克  我是醫院的希拉
- Hello? - Patrick, it's Sheila from the hospital.
醫生讓他醒過來了
They're bringing him out of the coma.
什么時候
When?
你得快點過來
You need to get over here.
好
Okay.
他清醒了  不過得留意著他
He's conscious, but keep an eye on him.
有事按那個鈕  我們馬上過來
Hit that button, and we'll be right in.
好的  謝謝  護士
Okay, thank you, nurse.
杰森·列儂  你這混蛋命夠硬的
You are one tough S.O.B., Jason Lennon.
命真硬
You really are.
我在哪兒
Where am I?
出什么事了
What happened?
你在薩克拉門托  你中槍了
You're in Sacramento. You got shot.
記得嗎
Do you remember that?
記得
Yes, I do.
勞拉蕾·馬丁斯開的槍
Lorelei Martins.
沒錯  很好  很好  你頭腦清楚了
Correct. Very good. Good. Your mind is clear.
現在聽著  我有個問題要問你  杰森
Now listen, I have a question for you, Jason.
看著我
Look at me.
看仔細了
Look close.
認識我嗎
You recognize me?
以前見過我沒有
You ever seen me before?
沒有
No.
確定嗎  這很重要
Are you sure? It's important.
是的
Yes.
我確定
I'm sure.
這就好  謝謝
That's good to know. Thanks.
你是誰
Who are you?
一個朋友
I'm a friend.
談點兒實際的吧  杰森
Let's face facts, Jason.
你要是恢復了  活了下來
If you recover and live,
會被控謀殺  蹲一輩子大牢
you'll spend life in prison for murder--
淪為那些變態的玩物
the plaything of monsters.
要是換做我
I just hope that if I'm ever in your shoes,
我希望能有個好朋友為我做這件事
I have a friend close enough to do this for me.
等等
Wait.
別怕
Don't be scared.
很快的
This'll be quick.
不怎么痛
Very little pain.
沒事  好了
It's okay. It's all right.
沒事的  我在這兒陪你
It's okay. I'm here for you.
我不會走的
I won't leave you.
來人啊  護士
Help! Nurse!
護士
Nurse!
是室顫
He's in V-fib.
把急救車推進來
Get that crash cart over here.
怎么了
What happened?
派翠克  很遺憾
Patrick, I'm sorry.
他心臟衰竭
His heart gave out.
一句話都沒留下
Never said a word.